Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 115, Folder: 14 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    June 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 4, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    August 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 5, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    October, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    December, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 22, No. 1, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    February, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 22, No. 2, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    April, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 22, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    May-June, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 22, No. 4, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    July, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 22, No. 5, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    October, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 22, No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    December, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 1, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    February 1, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 2, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    March 1, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    April 1, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 4, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    June 15, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 5, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    August 1, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    October 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 21, No. 7, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    December, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 1, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    January 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 2, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    February 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    March 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 4, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    April 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 5, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    May 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    June 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 7, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    July 15, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 8, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    September 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 9, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    October 15, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 10, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    November 15, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 11, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    December 15, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 1, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    January 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 2, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    February 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    March 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 4, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    April 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 5, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    May 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    June 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 7, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    July 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 8, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    September 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 9, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    October 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 10, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    November 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 11, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    December 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 18, No. 5, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    September 15, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 18, No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    October 15, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 18, No. 7, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    November 15, 1958. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 15 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Manual of Information Concerning Employments for Service on the Isthmus of Panama, Publication (Box 115, Folder 15)
    Revised January 3, 1908. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 16 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A Progrma for U.S. Energy Development, Publication (Box 115, Folder 16)
    January 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Constitution of the U.S. Labor Party, Publication (Box 115, Folder 16)
    By Lyndon H. LaRouche, Jr. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 17 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan Book and Membership Card, Publication (Box 115, Folder 17)
- Box: 115, Folder: 18 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Official Courtesy and Customs of the Service, Publication (Box 115, Folder 18)
    By The Department of Tactics. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 1 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Wartime Experiences of the National Labor Relations Board (1941-1945), Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    By Fred Whitney. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Studies of the Results of National Labor Relations Board Activities: A Summary of Operations Analysis, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    1942-1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Guide to the NLRA (National Labor Relations Act): Procedures and Practices, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Social Action: The National Labor Relations Board--Why and How--, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    By Louis Stark. August 16, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Politics and Labor Relations--N.L.R.B. Procedure, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    By Walter Gellhorm, Seymour L. Linfield. March, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: List of References on National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    By Bernard W. Stern. October 1, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: National Labor Relations Board Rules and Regulations Series 5 and Statements of Procedure as Amended August 18, 1948, Labor Management Relations Act, 1947, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: National Labor Relations Board: Rules and Regulations Series 3 as Amended and National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Effective July 12, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Problems of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Box: 116, Folder: 2 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Final Report of Work--Training with the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
    By Fred O. Board. June 16-August 20 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 3 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Career America, Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Key Presidential Appointments, Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
    January 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 4 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Authority of the National War Labor Board over Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    By Leonard B. Boudin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Proceedings: Before the Members, Staff and Guests of the National War LaborBoard on the Occasion of its Third Anniversary Dinner, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    January 13, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: WLB What it is How it Operates, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    June, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: National War Labor Board: Rules of Organization and Procedure for the National and Regional Boards, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    March 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Authority of the National War Labor Board Over Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The National War Labor Board: The Evolution of a National Wage Policy, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    By Robert Hachenburg. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Principles and Rules of Procedure, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Statement on the Work of the National War Labor Board, Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    January, 1942-January, 1944. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 5 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Price Control Laws and Executive Orders as Amended August 1946, Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Box: 116, Folder: 6 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Meeting the Need for Skilled Workers in a New Airplane Engine Plant Example No. 4, Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Upgrading and Fulltime Instructors Solve Problems of Expansion in Radio Manuafacture Example No. 5, Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Training for Quick Production in Heavy Manufacture Example No. 6, Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Upgrading and Training in a Large Steel Corporation Exampe No. 9, Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
- Box: 116, Folder: 7 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Program for Economic Seurity: President's Committee on Economic Security, Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Box: 116, Folder: 8 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report to the President, Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
    By W.G. McAdoo. September 3, 1918. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 9 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: United States Railroad Labor Board Chicago, Illinois: Average Wage Rates and General Rules of RailroadEmployees on Class I Carriers, Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    April, 1926. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 10 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: U.S. Railroad Retirement Board: A Manual for Supervisors, Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
- Box: 116, Folder: 11 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Welcome Family Day: Milan Footwear Plant, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    October 21, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United States Rubber Company Ideas Suggestion Plan: Los Angeles Plant, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: United States Rubber Company Suggestion Plan: Indianapolis Plant, Thinking Pays, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Effective August 1, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: United State Rubber Company Presents a Suggestion Plan for All Employees of the Gillette Tire Plant, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Mill Room Supervision: Training Manual, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    May 20, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Training and Operation Program for Truck Drivers, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Aygyst 14, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor Standards and Wage Payment Training Program, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    August 12, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Discussions with an Individual about Himself, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Industrial Relations Activities in the United States Rubber Company, Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
- Box: 116, Folder: 12 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Memoradum: Special Committee on Aging United States Senate, Publication (Box 116, Folder 12)
    May 18, 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 13 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: If You are Laid Off: Here's How to Get Your Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 116, Folder 13)
    November 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Why Social Security?, Publication (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Why Social Security?, Publication (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: A Handbook on Federal Old-Age and Survivors Insurance as provided in the Social Security Act, Publication (Box 116, Folder 13)
- Box: 116, Folder: 14 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Trades Apprenticeship in U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Paths of Opportunity in U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Service Fund Plan: Elmira Plant American Bridge Division, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Impromtu Remarks by Elbert H. Gary, Chairman at Annual Meeting of Stockholders United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Elbert H. Gary, Mr. Darwin P. Kingsley, Hon. Nathan L. Miller. April 18, 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Target for Termites, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Statement by Benjamin F. Fairless before the Wage Stabilization Board, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. February 4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Today's Costs of Tomorrow's Pensions, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Item is in English.
  - Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Information About Forthcoming Negotiations, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Toward a Point of No Return, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Basic Facts about United States Steel: The Industrial Family that Serves the Nation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Statemennts of Enders M. Voorhees before National War Labor Board Steel Panel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    May 23, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Welfare Work in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Charles L. Close. May 28, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Principles and Policies of the United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Elbert H. Gary. April 18, 1921. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: How Can You Beat the Heat!, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Television Station T-U-B-E brings you the latest reports on the Safety Records of Lorain, National, Ellwood, Gary, Christy Park Works, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: You The West and Columbia Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Proceedings at Annual Meeting of the Stockholders of The United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    April 20, 1914. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Safety Manual Heavy Duty Truck and Tractor Operation: Oiler Iron Mining Company, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Keep the Green Light Burning for Safety Plus!, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Safety in the Woodshop, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: The Coal Miner Issue No. 128, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    July 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Management's Responsibility in Industry, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By Irving S. Olds. May 27, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Save for Your Independence: U.S. Savings Bond Rally, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    October 10, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Charles M. Schwab, Publication (Box 116, Folder 14)
    By E.G. Grace. Item is in English.
- Box: 116, Folder: 15 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Organizing of Industrial Engineering Activities, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By R. Conrad Cooper. February 18, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Application for Employment: United States Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: United States Steel Corporatio: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: No. 183 Measuring Clerical Work, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By L. Browne Helms, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Fair Day's Work, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By J. L. Turner. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: No. 186 A Scientific Approach to Clerical Cost Control, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By H. F. Van Gorder. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Careers in Management, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    1975-1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Your Career in Internal Auditing with United States Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Chemical Careers in United States Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: No. 101 Organizing Management for Effective Training, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By F. J. Burtt. March 12, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: A Half Century of Industrial Progress With Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By M. W. Reed. April 26-28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Paths of Opportunity in U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Wage Chronology No. 3: United States Steel Corp., 1937-48, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Steel Making in America, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Douglas A. Fisher. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Your Business and Mine, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Price and Public Interest, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Roger M. Blough. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Great Myth, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Roger M. Blough. August 8, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Inflation or Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Irving S. Olds. April 24, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Guilty Before Trial, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. May 18, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: United States Steel's Reply to Demands of the United Steelworkers of Aerica (CIO), Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    July 6, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Variance Analysis for Reduction and Control Manufacturing Costs, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By John Pugsley. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: U.S. Steel's Policies on Costs, Prices, Plants, Productivity: First Disclosure of Iron Ore Discovery in Venezuela, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    January 24, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. January 23, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Item 25: Detour Ahead, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. April 21, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Statement on Steel Price Reduction, Publication (Box 116, Folder 15)
- Box: 116, Folder: 16 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Great Myth, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Roger M. Blough. April 8, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United States Steel Replies to the Union Demand for a $2 a Day Wage Increase, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Program of Insurance Benefits: Hourly Paid Employees, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    Amended September 1, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Letter to the President of the United States, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Hon. Harry S. Truman. January18, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Meet the Press: America's Pres Conference of the Air, an interview with Irving S. Olds, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    March 31, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Dear Mr. President An exchange of correspondence on steel prices between The President of the United States and Roger M. Blough, Chairman of the Board of United States Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Can A Free Economy Tolerate Union Violence?, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. February 25, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Man's Search for Secruity, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address given December 13, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: What Price, Controls?, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Irving S. Olds. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Research, Security and Progress, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Dr. R. E. Zimmerman. May 25, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Uncommon Man, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Enders M. Voorhees. May 26, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Some Economic Aspects of the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Dr. R. E. Zimmerman. Address given May 20, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Some Aspects of the Proposed Guaranteed Wage, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Irving S. Olds. May 14, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Settlement of the Strike Against United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Settlement of the Strike Against United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: The Fourth Dimension, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Leslie B. Worthington. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Passport to Progress, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address given October 31, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Our Privileged Milions, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: The Uncommon Man, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Enders M. Voohees. Address Given May 26, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: United States Steel Replies to the Union Demand for a $2 a Day Wage Increase, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 21: United States Steel Replies to the Union Demand for a $2 a Day Wage Increase, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 22: A Report to the Boss, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 23: Another Look at Wage Inflation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given April 2, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Remarks of Enders M. Voorhees Chairman of Finance Committee United States Steel Corporation before Te Finance Committee of the United States Senate, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Enders M. Voorhees. December 4, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Price and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 26: Mature Collectivve Bargaining-Prospects and Problems, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By John A. Stephens. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Insurance Benefits Plan for Participating Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    Revised November 1, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Working Man's Best Friend, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 29: The Working Man's Best Friend, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 30: United States Steel Replies to the Union Demand for a $2 a Day Wage Increase, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 31: Statement as to Wages, Hours and Other Conditions of Labor Among Employees of The United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 32: BusinessBig and SmallBuilt America, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Statement Given April 26-28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Statement by Benjamin F. Fairless before the Joint Committee on the Economic Report, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Benjamin F. Franklin. March 2, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: United States Steel Corporation Letter to the Stockholders of United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    October 1, 1949. Item is in English.